Jewish ritual slaughter.
Clashing with activists to the rescue.
Light it away, put it back!
Put it back, you see me?
He saw it.
Stop telling me anything.
I don't give a shit what you have to say.
Children and chickens caught in the middle.
This is part one of Christ-Piracy, a horror movie.
This week, up to 100,000 chickens
will die in New York alone to carry away human sin.
It's called Kipporah, and I'm spending all week
in the middle of it.
Activists pulling injured birds out of crates.
That's the bone sticking out.
Rituals happening on the sidewalk,
and children and chickens screaming
over what God actually wants.
So I started asking the question,
did God ever command this?
Is this in the Torah?
It's not in business, no.
Because the prophets say something different.
Hosea 6-6, I desire Pesach.
Mercy, not sacrifice.
The rabbis came, and they said, we should do this.
But did God, did Hashem say that?
Yes, no, a lot of things.
And everyone's giving me different answers
to the same questions.
Did the sins go into the chicken or no?
What do you mean the sins?
The sin is transferring to the chicken.
We hope.
So the sin transfers to the chicken?
No, it's just a reminder for us
to go to the Smith field,
and go to the meat packing plants over there
and take care of them.
It's no different.
Does someone eat these chickens?
All the chickens are being eaten.
Yeah, where do they go?
Come back in the store, the store.
To this store?
To all the stores.
Oh, okay.
Then someone eats the sins in the chicken
from the meat store?
No, I want it to get slaughtered.
The sins are gone when it's slaughtered.
It's not stuck in the blood?
So the sin is in the blood?
Yes.
It is in the blood.
Okay, this is a slaughterhouse?
Yes. Right here?
Yes.
So do these chickens?
Donate it.
Okay.
Where is it donated?
It's donated to the people who need it.
Where do people eat these chickens?
It goes to the slaughterhouse.
It goes to the slaughterhouse and people eat them?
Yes, absolutely.
So are they eating the sins?
Yeah, but what happens?
You must be single, huh?
You have nothing alive to do.
Huh?
Get yourself alive.
I'm out here every day this week,
building up to the final bloody day of atonement,
asking questions and filming everything.
This is a public sidewalk.
The boss, he's gonna call police.
The boss?
Who's the boss?
Can I see the slaughter?
No, but better for you than not for you.
Why?
They are very holy.
This is not the holiest thing for them.
Why not?
Can you ask him if I can just see him?
On Saturday for Yom Kippur,
they're gonna slaughter in the streets, yeah?
Yes.
So then I can see it there.
And at the end of this week,
something happens that I can't show you yet,
but trust me, many lives are about to change.
Comet Mercy for the full film about ritual sacrifice
at the core of corruption that Netflix tried to censor.